# John O'Connor johnpoconnor4@gmail.com 086-2392137

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Web developer with extensive experience in engineering project management. Proficient in object oriented programming. Knowledge of database management using SQL and MongoDB. Able to manage codebases through Git. Sample websites and source code can be found on my github page: https://github.com/Johnp179

## **EDUCATION**

Higher Diploma in Science in Computing	Griffith College Dublin	2017 - 2018
Master of Engineering in Biomedical Engineering	University College Dublin	2012 - 2014
Bachelors of Science in Mechanical Engineering	University College Dublin	2009 - 2012
Leaving Certificate - 465/600pts	St Peter's College	2003 –2009

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2015 – Feb 2022 **Project Engineer** BOC Gases Ireland

#### **Duties:**

- Surveying projects to determine the technical requirements.
- Issuing quotations.
- Managing the project: ordering materials, co-ordinating the installation, producing method statements and commissioning documentation.
- Issuing invoices.

July 2014 – Aug 2014 **Researcher** Technische Universität Ilmenau

#### **Duties:**

- Designed and constructed the experiment which consisted of a laser, sample mounted on a motor to produce small displacements and a camera.
- Developed the software which controlled the motor, camera and analysed the results obtained to determine characteristics of the sample.

# **REFERENCES**

References available upon request.